[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the Red Foxs lifespan in the wild?", "correct_answer": "3 years", "incorrect_answers": ["8 years", "6 years", "10 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the six-wheeled robotic vehicle of the Pathfinder Mission on Mars?", "correct_answer": "Sojourner", "incorrect_answers": ["Viking", "Mariner", "Pathfinder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Edaphic deserts can be found on some volcanic islands, in parts of Iceland and on the Colorado plateau in the USA. Which of these most accurately defines an edaphic desert?", "correct_answer": "One that gets enough rain but still lacks plants", "incorrect_answers": ["One that gets less than 2.5 cm of rain a year", "One that is so cold that nothing can grow", "One that has been a desert for at least 1 million years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor, featured in Its  A Wonderful Life (1946) appeared in the most Top 100 American films?", "correct_answer": "Ward Bond", "incorrect_answers": ["Agnes Moorehead", "John Turturro", "Walter Brennan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the proverb:\n\nPoets are born, ________.", "correct_answer": "...not made.", "incorrect_answers": ["...but can also be made.", "...but thats not for sure.", "..., long live the poets!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Henry Wheeler Shaw is responsible for this eponym.", "correct_answer": "josh", "incorrect_answers": ["trouser", "scrimshaw", "tuxedo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the weight range of normal mature platypuses?", "correct_answer": "From 0.7 to 2.4 kg", "incorrect_answers": ["Between 3.2 and 4.6 kg", "From 2.5 to 5.5 kg", "Between 0.5 to 2.8 kg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oliver Stones 1999 movie Any Given Sunday is about a fictional team competing in what sport?", "correct_answer": "American football", "incorrect_answers": ["Baseball", "Tennis", "Boxing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cranberries are known for preventing infections of this system in the human body.", "correct_answer": "Urinary system", "incorrect_answers": ["Vascular system", "Gastrointestinal system", "Nervous system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are seven tall buildings in Moscow, regarded as typical examples of Stalinist Architecture. What are these similarly designed buildings referred to?", "correct_answer": "\u2018Stalin\u2019s Seven Sisters\u2019", "incorrect_answers": ["\u2018Stalin\u2019s Seven Wonders\u2019", "\u2018Stalin\u2019s Seven Giants\u2019", "\u2018Stalin\u2019s Seven Brothers\u2019"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What problem of human society is largely treated in the 1993 drama movie Philadelphia, starring Tom Hanks?", "correct_answer": "Discrimination", "incorrect_answers": ["Illiteracy", "Corruption", "War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where can the polar bear be found?", "correct_answer": "Arctic", "incorrect_answers": ["South Pole", "Antartica", "All of these"]}]